<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bounty on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/tags/bounty/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bounty on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/tags/bounty/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Bounty and Hackathon Extended!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Dear Community, We hope you&amp;rsquo;ve been enjoying the bounty and hackathon so far. Thank you for all your excellent content submissions and signal boosting of our own content.
Our community and network have both grown enormously, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been able to make huge efficiency improvements to our app and chain based on your feedback and bug reports.
We&amp;rsquo;ve recently translated the bounty into Chinese to reach our community. Participation has been through the roof, with a consistent flow of new members signing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos $150k Bounty and Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Stegos $150,000 Bounty and Hackathon To celebrate our final testnet release before the upcoming Stegos IEO and mainnet release, we&amp;rsquo;re offering a $150,000 bounty program to help spread the word about Stegos and collect feedback on our app and blockchain.
The bounty program will run in two parts, each with a prize pool of $75,000 in STG coins. The two halves of the bounty program will run simultaneously, and you can take part in both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos News: $150k bounty and more!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3-and-150k-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3-and-150k-bounty/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, Big news this week. The devs have released the next beta version of mainnet: Mainnet Beta 3. This will be the final test version of mainnet before our release. You can read the full release notes here.
This week also marks the launch of our bounty and hackathon, where you can complete tasks to earn a share of $150,000 of STG. The bounty will have two halves: a social media contest running on our website and powered by the Vyper competition platform, and a hackathon hosted on our very own mainnet beta chain and supported by a Telegram bounty bot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>