<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 3 and App v0.14.0 Released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We&amp;rsquo;re please to announce our final beta release for the upcoming Stegos mainnet, as well as the next version of our desktop app (v0.14.0). The label &amp;ldquo;beta&amp;rdquo; means that we have no known critical issues and showstoppers. This is a complete restart of the chain, so all balances will be wiped. Users will have to delete their old chain data before restarting the app. The contents of the following directories must be deleted fully:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of AMA with BlockArk</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/ama-with-blockark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/ama-with-blockark/</guid>
      <description>At 7pm on September 17th, Stegos founder Joel conducted a 100-minute AMA live broadcast to the community. It was broadcast simultaneously across 9 different communities, with a peak viewership of 4,500 people as Joel shared the twists and turns of creating Stegos. The technical details of Stegos and the live Q&amp;amp;A discussion format made for an exciting evening. Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find a transcript of last night&amp;rsquo;s AMA.
This guest for this time is Joel, who is the founder of Stegos, an experienced hacker and blockchain pioneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 2 Released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/mainnet-beta-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/mainnet-beta-2/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, Thank you for all your testing feedback. We’re pleased to announce the release of Mainnet Beta 2. In addition to lots of improvements and UI tweaks, the most exciting feature of Mainnet Beta 2 is Windows support. So you can now use the app on Mac, Linux or Windows.
Please visit releases to download the app.
As always, please send comments, bug reports and any other feedback to support@stegos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta and Desktop App Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/first-desktop-app-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/first-desktop-app-beta/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We’re excited to present the first version of the Stegos desktop app. Our development team have poured their hearts into making this, and now we’d love for you to help us test it. Please download the app and use the test STG faucet to get some test STG to put it through its paces! ​ This is the very first public version of the app, so it’s still a work in progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMA session conducted over Telegram and Wechat, August 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/ama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/ama/</guid>
      <description>Host ： Hello, and welcome to this Stegos community AMA event. Our AMA is about to begin! Please don’t post messages during the AMA. We will begin by answering the questions we collected in advance, followed by a 15-minute quickfire question session to conclude the AMA.
Host ：Please welcome Stegos CEO Joel Reymont!
Host ：Hi Joel, welcome to the community and this AMA!
To start, Joel will outline Stegos&amp;rsquo; current status and future development vision, and share his experience of starting Stegos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Progress Report July, 16th - August, 5th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/tech-report-july-16th-august-5th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/tech-report-july-16th-august-5th/</guid>
      <description>Development Report July 16th – August 5th Hello, and welcome to the Stegos Development report for our 21st Sprint, covering the period from July 16th through August 5th.
We’ve mostly been concentrating on the Stegos GUI wallet. The Linux and iOS versions of the wallet are finished and being tested internally. Public testing will be announced shortly.
 Snowball improvements  We’ve been working to improve Stegos’ state-of-the-art mixing protocol, known as Snowball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stealth Mode Deactivated</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/88-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/88-news/</guid>
      <description>Dear Community, First of all, I&amp;rsquo;d like to apologize for the lack of updates: when you&amp;rsquo;re as serious about privacy as we are at Stegos, it can be hard to strike the right balance between secrecy and sharing! Rest assured, the whole team has been working hard behind the scenes on the Stegos chain, app, and a LOT of new marketing content, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t done a good enough job of keeping you, our loyal community, up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 4</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/mainnet-4-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/mainnet-4-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a bug fix release, containing more than 100 fixes since Mainnet Preview 3.
Changes in Stegos v0.11:  Improved overall stability and performance of Snowball mixing protocol, now Snowball works reliably even on slow 3G/4G mobile data connections. Tuned core blockchain constants and limits to reach the inflation target, now a new block is produced every 6-8 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Progress Report July, 1st - July, 15th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/tech-report-july-1st-july-15th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/tech-report-july-1st-july-15th/</guid>
      <description>Development Report July 1st – July 15th Hello, and welcome to the Stegos Development report for our 20th Sprint, covering the period from July 1st through July 15th.
The entire development team has been firing on all pistons in preparation for the launch of our mainnet. With the launch just a few weeks away, most of our hard work has been geared towards testing the blockchain and putting finishing touches to the Stegos app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 3</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-3-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-3-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a third Preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. In order to boost node synchronization and bootstrap performance we have switched to the new pairing curve, BLS12-381, reducing BLS signature verification by the factor of 40. Another major achievement was switching single curve crypto from Curve1174 to Curve25519 in order to increase Bulletproofs performance and provide a compatibility to iOS13 CryptoKit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report June, 17th - July, 1st</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-17th-july-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-17th-july-1st/</guid>
      <description>Done in Sprint 19  Switched to new pairing-based crypto implementation based on BLS12-381 curve, [Crypto], 40x improvement in BLS signature verification time Switched to Dalek Curve25519 implementation for single curve crypto, [Crypto], 10x improvement in Bulletproof verification time, future compatibility with iOS CryptoKit Implemented of Payment Certificates in CLI Wallet, [Wallet], payment certificates are needed if you have to proof that you send a particular amount of tokens to somebody</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 2</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-2-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a second Preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. We declare the feature freeze with this release - no new features are planned until the upcoming mainnet release. Of course, some minor improvements and bug fixes will be made until the final mainnet release.
New in Stegos v0.9:  Node has been split into two binaries: a full node daemon (stegosd) and a command-line client (stegos).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report June, 3rd - June, 17th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-3rd-june-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-3rd-june-17th/</guid>
      <description> Done in Sprint 18  Base functionality of GUI Wallet desktop application, Wallet, implementing bootstrapping visualisation, accounts and payments Persist Payment History and Payment Certificates in Wallet, Wallet, required to support showing the payment history in wallet Improve security of Docker image, Security, strengthen the security of the node&amp;rsquo;s docker image Introduce variable fees in transactions, Core Blockchain, Wallet, introduce the ability to set arbitrary fee amount for transaction in order to increase chances of transaction to be included in the nearest block Use Base58 for external representation of wallet public keys (addresses), Core Blockchain, provide more user-friendly encoding of addresses Implement WebSocket API Authorization, Security, introduce API tokens for authorizing WebSockets API usage, even on localhost Support changing the wallet password, Security, provide the ability for the user to change wallet password Stress Testing: Large Number of Nodes, Testing, part of test harness Split log output and CLI, Node CLI, separating CLI application from node binary Introduce variable fees in transactions, Core Blockchain, Wallet, introduce the ability to set arbitrary fee amount for transaction in order to increase chances of transaction to be included in the nearest block Speed up BLS signatures, Core Blockchain, BLS signature verification time has been improved from 200ms down to 5ms per signature  Plans for Sprint 19  Stress Testing: Packet Delay and Loss, Testing, part of test harness Stress Testing: Blockchain, Consensus, Service Awards, Slashing, ValueShuffle, Testing, stress testing the vital subsystems using transactional loads from transaction generator  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 1</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-1-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Mainnet Preview 1 Release Notes Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a first preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. This preview version is considered mostly feature-complete. All core features have been implemented, yet some improvements and bug fixes need to be made for the final release.
New in Stegos v0.8:  Created an innovative blockchain compression technology to remove intermediate intra-epoch blocks after reaching the final pBFT consensus in validators group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 7 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-7-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-7-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the seventh testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 6:
 New StakeUTXO, Core Blockchain, StakeUTXOs with BLS signatures Public payment UTXO, Core Blockchain, UTXO with uncloaked recipient pubkey and amount Adding time locks to all UTXO types, Core Blockchain, allow UTXOs to be time-locked Introducing micro and macro blocks, Core Blockchain, adding more security to microblocks Slashing, Consensus, punishing the cheating slot owner for publishing two different blocks on the same height Re-Staking, Consensus, changing validators’ PBC keys related to staked tokens at the predetermined intervals Stabilize ValueShuffle facilitating in the event of epoch change, ValueShuffle, fine-tuning of the Facilitator code Change PBC keys: network, Network, support for changing node’s pbc (validator) keys on the go Check for stale connections, Network, check if some neighbor connections are stale and re-connect Stress Testing: Deploy TxGenerator, Testing, transaction generator deployment support for devnets Use AONT (All or Nothing) for all serialized representation of secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets Implement WAU (Wipe After Use) for all secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets  Breaking changes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report May, 6th - May, 17th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period May, 6th — May, 17th:
Done in Sprint 16
 New StakeUTXO, Core Blockchain, StakeUTXOs with BLS signatures Public payment UTXO, Core Blockchain, UTXO with uncloaked recipient pubkey and amount Adding time locks to all UTXO types, Core Blockchain, allow UTXOs to be time-locked Introducing micro and macro blocks, Core Blockchain, adding more security to microblocks Slashing, Consensus, punishing the cheating slot owner for publishing two different blocks on the same height Re-Staking, Consensus, changing validators’ PBC keys related to staked tokens at the predetermined intervals Stabilize ValueShuffle facilitating in the event of epoch change, ValueShuffle, fine-tuning of the Facilitator code Change PBC keys: network, Network, support for changing node’s pbc (validator) keys on the go Check for stale connections, Network, check if some neighbor connections are stale and re-connect Stress Testing: Deploy TxGenerator, Testing, transaction generator deployment support for devnets Use AONT (All or Nothing) for all serialized representation of secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets Implement WAU (Wipe After Use) for all secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets  Plans for Sprint 17</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 6 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 6 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the sixth Testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 5:
 Added HashCash challenge to PubSub protocol to limit denial-of-service attacks Implemented simplified Re-Staking for tracking validators&amp;rsquo; online status Implemented wallet recovery using 24-word recovery phrase Implemented wallet password protection and encryption of keys stored on disk Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 microSTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report May, 20th - May, 31st</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-20th-may-31st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-20th-may-31st/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period May, 20th — May, 31st:
Done in Sprint 17  Speed-up node bootstrap and re-synchronization, Node, fine-tuning bootstrap constants
 Service Awards, Core Blockchain, required to create an incentive for validators to be always online
 Compress Micro Blocks to Macro Blocks, Consensus, remove last epoch’s micro blocks by moving their data to a single macro block</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 22nd - May, 3rd </title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period April, 22nd — May, 3rd:
Done
 Finalize HashCash integration, Network, required to prevent DoS-attacks Stress Testing: Transactional Load Generator, Testing, the part of test harness Determine major blockchain constants: Maximum UTXOs per Block, Epoch Length &amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, those are important parameters of the consensus protocol Wallet Recovery, Wallet, required to recover wallet keys using 24-word recovery phrase Key Encryption on the Disk, Wallet, implement safe storage of keys on disk Proof of UTXO Construction, Wallet, a feature allowing to prove that a particular transaction has taken place in the past  In progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 8th - Apr, 19th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April,8th — April, 19th:
Done
 Kademlia DHT-based routing, Network, base networking functionality for unicast messages Research xPIR, Experimental, research the possibility of using private information retrieval protocols to secure light nodes Websocket Wallet API Enhancements Fork Resolution, Consensus, this is an essential part of the consensus protocol Rollback of Payment Transactions in Wallet, Wallet, this mechanism is needed due to fork resolution Limit the Number of Outputs in a Block, Core Blockchain, required to prevent traffic jams in the network Stabilize Network, Network, testing and bug fixing Stabilize Consensus, Consensus, testing and bug fixing Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 Units (microSTG), Core Blockchain, required to have fractional STG units  Plans for Sprint 15</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 5 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 5 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the fifth testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 4:
 Added a fork resolution mechanism to consensus and improved handling of network partitions. Implemented basic cheating detection of malicious validators in consensus (without punishment for now). Significantly reduced the time of full sync with the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mobile Blockchain - The Holy Grail</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/mobile-blockchain-the-holy-grail/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/mobile-blockchain-the-holy-grail/</guid>
      <description>The Holy Grail
Mobile blockchain is the crypto Holy Grail. If we&amp;rsquo;re creating a global decentralized network of millions of users, we&amp;rsquo;ll want it to run on the simplest devices possible. But this has often been dismissed as too difficult, so developers either treat smartphone support as a long-term goal (which they never get to), completely neuter the capabilities of their mobile nodes, or ignore them entirely.
But that’s completely the wrong approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Tech Report Mar, 25th - Apr, 5th”</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April, 2nd — April, 15th:
 Investigate packet loss in libp2p, Network, fixing a bug with lost packets related to the usage of Cuckoo-filters View Changes for Micro Blocks, Consensus, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol View Changes for Key Blocks, Consensus`, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol Determine Epoch Length &amp;amp;&amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, epoch length and block time are important parameters of the consensus protocol HashCash Algorithm, Network, nodes have to solve HashCash puzzles in order to join the network to prevent Sybil attacks Unicast Messages Encryption, Network, unicast messages traveling over Kademlia DHT network have to be encrypted Test cases for block validation, Core Blockchain, part of the functional testing harness RaptorQ Encoder/Decoder, Network, required to create optimized protocol for transmission of blocks/other large messages  In-progress:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Contracts Are Useless</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/smart-contract-are-useless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 12:05:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/smart-contract-are-useless/</guid>
      <description>The ideas behind smart contracts are over twenty years old, but smart contracts only became a major talking point in the past five years, with the release of Ethereum and its Solidity programming language.
For much of 2017, you couldn’t move for ICOs promising to use smart contracts to revolutionize the way we transact and do business, and the cryptosphere is still awash with articles explaining the coming smart contract revolution, how smart contracts are going to disrupt everything from logistics to real estate, will put lawyers everywhere out of jobs, and render thousands of years of developments in human contract law obsolete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech report Jan, 29th - Feb, 8th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period January, 29th — February, 8th:
 Core: Blockchain persistency. Blocks are stored on disk now but no transaction pruning is applied. Core: Node bootstrap. A new node can connect to any Stegos nodes to download the blockchain. Core: The special Data UTXO type has been removed and data functionality has been rolled into the payment UTXO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards a crypto thaw: Using incentives to drive adoption</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/towards-a-ctypto-thaw-using-incentives-to-drive-adoption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:02:22 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/towards-a-ctypto-thaw-using-incentives-to-drive-adoption/</guid>
      <description>As the crypto winter stretches past the twelve-month mark, many people are asking what went wrong and when (or indeed if) it’s going to end.
But the diagnosis isn’t mysterious. And neither is the cure.
Fostering breathless excitement about price and moon lambos was always unsustainable. Yes, ICOs injected a lot of tokens into the ecosystem, but that’s not how you bootstrap. Cryptocurrencies only have value if they’re useful, so we need people to use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos: More trustless than ZCash, more scalable than Monero, more user-friendly than MimbleWimble</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/stegos-more-trustless-than-zcash-more-scalable-than-monero-more-user-friendly-than-mimblewimble/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/stegos-more-trustless-than-zcash-more-scalable-than-monero-more-user-friendly-than-mimblewimble/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of unprecedented state surveillance and crackdowns on freedom of transactions, expression, and even thought. But privacy is a universal human right that we must fight to preserve. There are various tools available which promise to ensure your privacy, such as encrypted email and messaging applications, but these leave highly visible clues about who you are and who you are talking to.
Stegos Privacy Blockchain is the best way to secure your data, transactions and communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech report Dec,31st - Jan, 27th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</guid>
      <description>Dec,31st - Jan,13th, the Stegos development team has released the blockchain prototype (MVP). The MVP release containts the following base features:
 Nodes can select a group of validators among them Nodes can elect a leader of the consensus Nodes can verify incoming transactions The leader of consensus can create and propose blocks Validators can verify proposed blocks and co-sign them with their BLS signature The leader can form the final BLS multi-signature and broadcast sealed block to the network Nodes can verify and process incoming sealed blocks by pruning spent UTXOs out of the UTXO set  There is no disk persistance in the MVP release, as well as new nodes cannot connect and bootstrap from the living nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>