<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>report on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/zn/tags/report/</link>
    <description>Recent content in report on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/zn/tags/report/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report May, 6th - May, 17th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period May, 6th — May, 17th:
Done in Sprint 16
 New StakeUTXO, Core Blockchain, StakeUTXOs with BLS signatures Public payment UTXO, Core Blockchain, UTXO with uncloaked recipient pubkey and amount Adding time locks to all UTXO types, Core Blockchain, allow UTXOs to be time-locked Introducing micro and macro blocks, Core Blockchain, adding more security to microblocks Slashing, Consensus, punishing the cheating slot owner for publishing two different blocks on the same height Re-Staking, Consensus, changing validators’ PBC keys related to staked tokens at the predetermined intervals Stabilize ValueShuffle facilitating in the event of epoch change, ValueShuffle, fine-tuning of the Facilitator code Change PBC keys: network, Network, support for changing node’s pbc (validator) keys on the go Check for stale connections, Network, check if some neighbor connections are stale and re-connect Stress Testing: Deploy TxGenerator, Testing, transaction generator deployment support for devnets Use AONT (All or Nothing) for all serialized representation of secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets Implement WAU (Wipe After Use) for all secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets  Plans for Sprint 17</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 6 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 6 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the sixth Testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 5:
 Added HashCash challenge to PubSub protocol to limit denial-of-service attacks Implemented simplified Re-Staking for tracking validators&amp;rsquo; online status Implemented wallet recovery using 24-word recovery phrase Implemented wallet password protection and encryption of keys stored on disk Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 microSTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 22nd - May, 3rd </title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period April, 22nd — May, 3rd:
Done
 Finalize HashCash integration, Network, required to prevent DoS-attacks Stress Testing: Transactional Load Generator, Testing, the part of test harness Determine major blockchain constants: Maximum UTXOs per Block, Epoch Length &amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, those are important parameters of the consensus protocol Wallet Recovery, Wallet, required to recover wallet keys using 24-word recovery phrase Key Encryption on the Disk, Wallet, implement safe storage of keys on disk Proof of UTXO Construction, Wallet, a feature allowing to prove that a particular transaction has taken place in the past  In progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 8th - Apr, 19th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April,8th — April, 19th:
Done
 Kademlia DHT-based routing, Network, base networking functionality for unicast messages Research xPIR, Experimental, research the possibility of using private information retrieval protocols to secure light nodes Websocket Wallet API Enhancements Fork Resolution, Consensus, this is an essential part of the consensus protocol Rollback of Payment Transactions in Wallet, Wallet, this mechanism is needed due to fork resolution Limit the Number of Outputs in a Block, Core Blockchain, required to prevent traffic jams in the network Stabilize Network, Network, testing and bug fixing Stabilize Consensus, Consensus, testing and bug fixing Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 Units (microSTG), Core Blockchain, required to have fractional STG units  Plans for Sprint 15</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 5 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 5 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the fifth testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 4:
 Added a fork resolution mechanism to consensus and improved handling of network partitions. Implemented basic cheating detection of malicious validators in consensus (without punishment for now). Significantly reduced the time of full sync with the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Tech Report Mar, 25th - Apr, 5th”</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April, 2nd — April, 15th:
 Investigate packet loss in libp2p, Network, fixing a bug with lost packets related to the usage of Cuckoo-filters View Changes for Micro Blocks, Consensus, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol View Changes for Key Blocks, Consensus`, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol Determine Epoch Length &amp;amp;&amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, epoch length and block time are important parameters of the consensus protocol HashCash Algorithm, Network, nodes have to solve HashCash puzzles in order to join the network to prevent Sybil attacks Unicast Messages Encryption, Network, unicast messages traveling over Kademlia DHT network have to be encrypted Test cases for block validation, Core Blockchain, part of the functional testing harness RaptorQ Encoder/Decoder, Network, required to create optimized protocol for transmission of blocks/other large messages  In-progress:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos技术周报（01.29 - 02.08）</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 14:03:09 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</guid>
      <description>在过去两周内，我们的开发团队一直在努力完成即将推出的testnet版本的主要功能。
1月29日 - 2月8日完成了以下任务：
 Core：区块链持续性。块现在存储在磁盘上，但未应用任何事务修剪； Core：节点引导程序。新节点可以连接到任何Stegos节点以下载区块链； Core：已删除特殊的数据UTXO类型，并且数据功能已滚入支付UTXO。ValueShuffle：DiceMix； ValueShuffle：组成超级交易。需要更多的单元测试； Networking：全球网络同行商店。基于Kademlia DHT； Networking：节点搜寻。包括节点认证； Networking：单播消息传递；  我们的下一个冲刺周期（sprint）将致力于彻底的测试，错误修复和启动第一个Stegos testnet！
2月11日 - 2月22日的任务：
测试：应用于事务处理，块处理，初始随机性（VRF），共识，持久性和引导的细致测试和错误修复。
 Core：节点CLI增强功能； Core：孤儿交易处理； Core：限制块的最大大小； ValueShuffle：第一个工作实施DevOps； 收集和处理指标和日志（Logstash，Prometheus，Grafana，ElasticSearch，Filebeat，Kibana等）； DevOps：AWS上的TestNet部署；  我们计划在冲刺周期10（Sprint 10）的第二周早些时候冻结新功能，以便在2月21日星期四之前发布testnet二进制文件并启动testnet。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos技术周报（2018.12.31更新)</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 17:06:33 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/zn/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</guid>
      <description>12月31日 - 1月13日，Stegos开发团队发布了区块链原型（MVP）。MVP版本包含以下基本功能：
 节点可以在他们中选出验证器组； 节点可以选出共识的领导者； 节点可以验证传入的事务； 共识的领导者可以创建和提出块； 验证器可以验证提出的块并使用他们的BLS签名共同对块进行签名； 领导者可以形成最终的BLS多重签名和广播密封的块到网络； MVP版本中没有磁盘持久性，新节点也无法与活动节点连接和引导；  1月14日 - 1月27日，我们的开发人员开始工作于提交testnet-1版本。该冲刺我们取得了一些成功，Stegos节点添加了以下功能：
 ValueShuffle的Diffie-Hellman密钥交换； ValueShuffle的DiceMix协议（需要更全面的测试覆盖）； ValueShuffle的交易池Facilitator选举； 针对共识和验证者组形成协议的杂项错误修复； 赌注和赎回交易； 区块奖励； 我们的网络、libp2p和floodsub已经更新到最新版本，最新版的libp2p引入了 很多突破性改进； Unicast Messaging（模拟）已经在新的floodsub版本之上重新引入； 全球区块链货币余额验证；  1月28日 – 2月10日的计划如下：
 研究更深入的分支和削减主题； 完成DiceMix； 完成Value Shuffle：超级交易形成及其广播； 用于功能测试、tx处理功能测试、块处理和选举的通用框架； Strawman磁盘持续性，完全未修剪的块； 节点引导程序； 网络层：基于Kademlia DHT的Peer Store； 网络层：Node Discovery协议； 网络层：节点之间的正确的（非模拟）单播消息传递； 网络层：跟踪Peer State；   请关注Stegos官方平台动态</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>