<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pools on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/tags/pools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pools on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/tags/pools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Staking Pools FAQ</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq/</guid>
      <description>This week marked the launch of the Stegos staking pools. You can find the launch announcement here, along with all the details about our first pool, The Vault, and the huge bonuses it brings!
This announcement generated a lot of excitement in the community, but also a lot of requests for more details. Here are the answers to some of the most common questions. If you still want to know more, contact one of the admins on our Telegram group, or head to the forums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready, Set, Stake!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools/</guid>
      <description>Don’t want to run a node? Don’t know how? Maybe you’re a little short on STG, or don’t have the resources or availability to run a reliable node of your own? Maybe you’ve got the opposite problem, and have some STG to spare? Don’t worry, we’ve got everyone covered. Stegos staking pools are here. While community infrastructure builds up in and around the Stegos network, we’re taking the initiative to put together a number of public staking pools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Staking Pools Just Got MUCH Simpler</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/simpler-staking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/simpler-staking/</guid>
      <description>At Stegos, we are committed to making things intuitive and user friendly. Our staking pools were created to make staking as accessible as possible, but KYC requirements went against this. So we got rid of them. Aggressive pruning, network sharding, and fast data messaging all prepare the Stegos network for worldwide adoption. In order to see that level of activity, our ecosystem of software and applications must be as easy to use and accessible as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>