<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>design on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/tags/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in design on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 12:05:29 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/tags/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Contracts Are Useless</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/smart-contract-are-useless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 12:05:29 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/smart-contract-are-useless/</guid>
      <description>The ideas behind smart contracts are over twenty years old, but smart contracts only became a major talking point in the past five years, with the release of Ethereum and its Solidity programming language.
For much of 2017, you couldn’t move for ICOs promising to use smart contracts to revolutionize the way we transact and do business, and the cryptosphere is still awash with articles explaining the coming smart contract revolution, how smart contracts are going to disrupt everything from logistics to real estate, will put lawyers everywhere out of jobs, and render thousands of years of developments in human contract law obsolete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Towards a crypto thaw: Using incentives to drive adoption</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/towards-a-ctypto-thaw-using-incentives-to-drive-adoption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:02:22 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/towards-a-ctypto-thaw-using-incentives-to-drive-adoption/</guid>
      <description>As the crypto winter stretches past the twelve-month mark, many people are asking what went wrong and when (or indeed if) it’s going to end.
But the diagnosis isn’t mysterious. And neither is the cure.
Fostering breathless excitement about price and moon lambos was always unsustainable. Yes, ICOs injected a lot of tokens into the ecosystem, but that’s not how you bootstrap. Cryptocurrencies only have value if they’re useful, so we need people to use them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos: More trustless than ZCash, more scalable than Monero, more user-friendly than MimbleWimble</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/stegos-more-trustless-than-zcash-more-scalable-than-monero-more-user-friendly-than-mimblewimble/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/stegos-more-trustless-than-zcash-more-scalable-than-monero-more-user-friendly-than-mimblewimble/</guid>
      <description>We live in an era of unprecedented state surveillance and crackdowns on freedom of transactions, expression, and even thought. But privacy is a universal human right that we must fight to preserve. There are various tools available which promise to ensure your privacy, such as encrypted email and messaging applications, but these leave highly visible clues about who you are and who you are talking to.
Stegos Privacy Blockchain is the best way to secure your data, transactions and communications.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>