<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DEVELOPMENT on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DEVELOPMENT on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Security: Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/practices/</guid>
      <description>Privacy and security go hand-and-hand, and the Stegos team is dedicated to ensuring the security of your Stegos nodes and funds, particularly when it comes to exchanges. But as with all crypto, ultimate responsibility lies with the user. Read on for some simple tips to help protect yourself against hackers and nefarious actors!
Our CEO Joel recently commented on the official Stegos Telegram channel about security measures, exchanges and how that translates to executive decisions by Stegos team, along with some strategies users can employ to protect their STG holdings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it Works: Gamified Proof-of-Stake (gPoS)!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/gpos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/gpos/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency design is often focused on security, scalability and decentralization, and rightly so. But that’s not enough to build large networks which can last for the long haul. At Stegos, we know that a cryptocurrency network also needs to be fun, engaging, surprising, and rewarding. Our gamified Proof-of-Stake (gPoS) system is built with exactly these qualities in mind. Read on to learn more about what gPoS is, how it works, why a balance of risk and reward helps promote engagement and decentralization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Staking Pools FAQ</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq/</guid>
      <description>This week marked the launch of the Stegos staking pools. You can find the launch announcement here, along with all the details about our first pool, The Vault, and the huge bonuses it brings!
This announcement generated a lot of excitement in the community, but also a lot of requests for more details. Here are the answers to some of the most common questions. If you still want to know more, contact one of the admins on our Telegram group, or head to the forums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready, Set, Stake!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools/</guid>
      <description>Don’t want to run a node? Don’t know how? Maybe you’re a little short on STG, or don’t have the resources or availability to run a reliable node of your own? Maybe you’ve got the opposite problem, and have some STG to spare? Don’t worry, we’ve got everyone covered. Stegos staking pools are here. While community infrastructure builds up in and around the Stegos network, we’re taking the initiative to put together a number of public staking pools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Discourse Forums Launch Announcement</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/discours-forums/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/discours-forums/</guid>
      <description>The Stegos Discourse Forums Have Arrived!
Stegos is a unique privacy network with many advanced and unusual features. This places Stegos a cut above the rest of the crypto pack, but it can also make it tricky for newcomers to just jump in. And for those who already know their way around our blockchain, it can be hard to find a place to discuss advanced topics or find the answers to tricky questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays from Stegos</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/12/happy-holidays-from-stegos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/12/happy-holidays-from-stegos/</guid>
      <description>Dear community, From our Stegos family to yours, we wish you happiness and peace this holiday season!
Regardless of what you celebrate, we hope you get some private time to relax and spend time with friends and family as the year comes to an end.
News Rundown The end of the year has been extremely busy at Stegos HQ. Here’s some of the things you might have missed:
Mainnet Launch The Stegos mainnet launched in November, and everything went very smoothly, thanks to all the bug testing and feedback from the community during the hackathon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce the release of the Stegos mainnet.
Please download v1.0 of the Stegos desktop app by selecting the file from the Assets menu at the bottom of the page which matches your operating system.
New Users If this is your first time using the Stegos app, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to do anything else. Just download and install the app and you&amp;rsquo;re ready to go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Launched!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launched-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launched-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce the successful launch of the Stegos mainnet!
Head here to download v1.0 of the Stegos destkop app and get started. Existing users should delete their testnet chain data and restart their app: it will update automatically.
What Next? This week we&amp;rsquo;re concentrating on sending everyone their STG coins. If we need any information from you, the team will be in touch directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Launch Announcement</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launch/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, After thousands of hours of development work, months of testing and six weeks of intense feedback and updates courtesy of our wonderful Stegos community and the bounty and hackathon, we&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce that the Stegos Mainnet will be launching on Wednesday 20th November!
STG Unlock Schedule We&amp;rsquo;re committed to a rapid unlock schedule to give everyone access to the STG they&amp;rsquo;ve bought and earned as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 5 Launched!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-beta-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-beta-5/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, This is the fifth beta release of the upcoming Stegos mainnet. Beta 5 is primarily a stabilization release, which fixes a major bug and brings many speed improvements. This release is fully compatible with Beta 4 Stegos blockchain and no other actions besides updating Stegos software is required from users.
Upgrading to Beta 5 is highly recommended, especially for participants of the bounty program.
Changes since Mainnet Beta 4:  Finally fixed DNS resolver on Windows Fixed multiple corner cases in consensus Fixed &amp;ldquo;entered unreachable code&amp;rdquo; bug Enabled log rotation for stegosd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Bounty and Hackathon Extended!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Dear Community, We hope you&amp;rsquo;ve been enjoying the bounty and hackathon so far. Thank you for all your excellent content submissions and signal boosting of our own content.
Our community and network have both grown enormously, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been able to make huge efficiency improvements to our app and chain based on your feedback and bug reports.
We&amp;rsquo;ve recently translated the bounty into Chinese to reach our community. Participation has been through the roof, with a consistent flow of new members signing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 4 released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-4/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community! We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce the fourth beta release of the upcoming Stegos mainnet, which fixes a major bug and brings many speed improvements.
VERY IMPORTANT!!!: This release involves a complete restart of the chain, SO PLEASE READ THE NEXT SECTION EXTREMELY CAREFULLY OR YOU MAY LOSE YOUR TOKENS AND HACKATHON PROGRESS.
Steps to install the new release If you are already participating in the bounty If you are an existing participant of the bounty program and have already received bounty tokens to your Stegos wallet, you MUST BACK UP YOUR ACCOUNT, otherwise all of your bounty tokens will be permanently lost!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos $150k Bounty and Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Stegos $150,000 Bounty and Hackathon To celebrate our final testnet release before the upcoming Stegos IEO and mainnet release, we&amp;rsquo;re offering a $150,000 bounty program to help spread the word about Stegos and collect feedback on our app and blockchain.
The bounty program will run in two parts, each with a prize pool of $75,000 in STG coins. The two halves of the bounty program will run simultaneously, and you can take part in both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos News: $150k bounty and more!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3-and-150k-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3-and-150k-bounty/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, Big news this week. The devs have released the next beta version of mainnet: Mainnet Beta 3. This will be the final test version of mainnet before our release. You can read the full release notes here.
This week also marks the launch of our bounty and hackathon, where you can complete tasks to earn a share of $150,000 of STG. The bounty will have two halves: a social media contest running on our website and powered by the Vyper competition platform, and a hackathon hosted on our very own mainnet beta chain and supported by a Telegram bounty bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 3 and App v0.14.0 Released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We&amp;rsquo;re please to announce our final beta release for the upcoming Stegos mainnet, as well as the next version of our desktop app (v0.14.0). The label &amp;ldquo;beta&amp;rdquo; means that we have no known critical issues and showstoppers. This is a complete restart of the chain, so all balances will be wiped. Users will have to delete their old chain data before restarting the app. The contents of the following directories must be deleted fully:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 2 Released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/mainnet-beta-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/mainnet-beta-2/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, Thank you for all your testing feedback. We’re pleased to announce the release of Mainnet Beta 2. In addition to lots of improvements and UI tweaks, the most exciting feature of Mainnet Beta 2 is Windows support. So you can now use the app on Mac, Linux or Windows.
Please visit releases to download the app.
As always, please send comments, bug reports and any other feedback to support@stegos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta and Desktop App Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/first-desktop-app-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/first-desktop-app-beta/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We’re excited to present the first version of the Stegos desktop app. Our development team have poured their hearts into making this, and now we’d love for you to help us test it. Please download the app and use the test STG faucet to get some test STG to put it through its paces! ​ This is the very first public version of the app, so it’s still a work in progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Progress Report July, 16th - August, 5th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/tech-report-july-16th-august-5th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/tech-report-july-16th-august-5th/</guid>
      <description>Development Report July 16th – August 5th Hello, and welcome to the Stegos Development report for our 21st Sprint, covering the period from July 16th through August 5th.
We’ve mostly been concentrating on the Stegos GUI wallet. The Linux and iOS versions of the wallet are finished and being tested internally. Public testing will be announced shortly.
 Snowball improvements  We’ve been working to improve Stegos’ state-of-the-art mixing protocol, known as Snowball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stealth Mode Deactivated</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/88-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/88-news/</guid>
      <description>Dear Community, First of all, I&amp;rsquo;d like to apologize for the lack of updates: when you&amp;rsquo;re as serious about privacy as we are at Stegos, it can be hard to strike the right balance between secrecy and sharing! Rest assured, the whole team has been working hard behind the scenes on the Stegos chain, app, and a LOT of new marketing content, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t done a good enough job of keeping you, our loyal community, up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 4</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/mainnet-4-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/mainnet-4-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a bug fix release, containing more than 100 fixes since Mainnet Preview 3.
Changes in Stegos v0.11:  Improved overall stability and performance of Snowball mixing protocol, now Snowball works reliably even on slow 3G/4G mobile data connections. Tuned core blockchain constants and limits to reach the inflation target, now a new block is produced every 6-8 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Progress Report July, 1st - July, 15th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/tech-report-july-1st-july-15th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/tech-report-july-1st-july-15th/</guid>
      <description>Development Report July 1st – July 15th Hello, and welcome to the Stegos Development report for our 20th Sprint, covering the period from July 1st through July 15th.
The entire development team has been firing on all pistons in preparation for the launch of our mainnet. With the launch just a few weeks away, most of our hard work has been geared towards testing the blockchain and putting finishing touches to the Stegos app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 3</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-3-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-3-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a third Preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. In order to boost node synchronization and bootstrap performance we have switched to the new pairing curve, BLS12-381, reducing BLS signature verification by the factor of 40. Another major achievement was switching single curve crypto from Curve1174 to Curve25519 in order to increase Bulletproofs performance and provide a compatibility to iOS13 CryptoKit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report June, 17th - July, 1st</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-17th-july-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-17th-july-1st/</guid>
      <description>Done in Sprint 19  Switched to new pairing-based crypto implementation based on BLS12-381 curve, [Crypto], 40x improvement in BLS signature verification time Switched to Dalek Curve25519 implementation for single curve crypto, [Crypto], 10x improvement in Bulletproof verification time, future compatibility with iOS CryptoKit Implemented of Payment Certificates in CLI Wallet, [Wallet], payment certificates are needed if you have to proof that you send a particular amount of tokens to somebody</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 2</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-2-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a second Preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. We declare the feature freeze with this release - no new features are planned until the upcoming mainnet release. Of course, some minor improvements and bug fixes will be made until the final mainnet release.
New in Stegos v0.9:  Node has been split into two binaries: a full node daemon (stegosd) and a command-line client (stegos).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report June, 3rd - June, 17th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-3rd-june-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-3rd-june-17th/</guid>
      <description> Done in Sprint 18  Base functionality of GUI Wallet desktop application, Wallet, implementing bootstrapping visualisation, accounts and payments Persist Payment History and Payment Certificates in Wallet, Wallet, required to support showing the payment history in wallet Improve security of Docker image, Security, strengthen the security of the node&amp;rsquo;s docker image Introduce variable fees in transactions, Core Blockchain, Wallet, introduce the ability to set arbitrary fee amount for transaction in order to increase chances of transaction to be included in the nearest block Use Base58 for external representation of wallet public keys (addresses), Core Blockchain, provide more user-friendly encoding of addresses Implement WebSocket API Authorization, Security, introduce API tokens for authorizing WebSockets API usage, even on localhost Support changing the wallet password, Security, provide the ability for the user to change wallet password Stress Testing: Large Number of Nodes, Testing, part of test harness Split log output and CLI, Node CLI, separating CLI application from node binary Introduce variable fees in transactions, Core Blockchain, Wallet, introduce the ability to set arbitrary fee amount for transaction in order to increase chances of transaction to be included in the nearest block Speed up BLS signatures, Core Blockchain, BLS signature verification time has been improved from 200ms down to 5ms per signature  Plans for Sprint 19  Stress Testing: Packet Delay and Loss, Testing, part of test harness Stress Testing: Blockchain, Consensus, Service Awards, Slashing, ValueShuffle, Testing, stress testing the vital subsystems using transactional loads from transaction generator  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 1</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-1-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Mainnet Preview 1 Release Notes Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a first preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. This preview version is considered mostly feature-complete. All core features have been implemented, yet some improvements and bug fixes need to be made for the final release.
New in Stegos v0.8:  Created an innovative blockchain compression technology to remove intermediate intra-epoch blocks after reaching the final pBFT consensus in validators group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 7 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-7-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-7-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the seventh testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 6:
 New StakeUTXO, Core Blockchain, StakeUTXOs with BLS signatures Public payment UTXO, Core Blockchain, UTXO with uncloaked recipient pubkey and amount Adding time locks to all UTXO types, Core Blockchain, allow UTXOs to be time-locked Introducing micro and macro blocks, Core Blockchain, adding more security to microblocks Slashing, Consensus, punishing the cheating slot owner for publishing two different blocks on the same height Re-Staking, Consensus, changing validators’ PBC keys related to staked tokens at the predetermined intervals Stabilize ValueShuffle facilitating in the event of epoch change, ValueShuffle, fine-tuning of the Facilitator code Change PBC keys: network, Network, support for changing node’s pbc (validator) keys on the go Check for stale connections, Network, check if some neighbor connections are stale and re-connect Stress Testing: Deploy TxGenerator, Testing, transaction generator deployment support for devnets Use AONT (All or Nothing) for all serialized representation of secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets Implement WAU (Wipe After Use) for all secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets  Breaking changes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report May, 6th - May, 17th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period May, 6th — May, 17th:
Done in Sprint 16
 New StakeUTXO, Core Blockchain, StakeUTXOs with BLS signatures Public payment UTXO, Core Blockchain, UTXO with uncloaked recipient pubkey and amount Adding time locks to all UTXO types, Core Blockchain, allow UTXOs to be time-locked Introducing micro and macro blocks, Core Blockchain, adding more security to microblocks Slashing, Consensus, punishing the cheating slot owner for publishing two different blocks on the same height Re-Staking, Consensus, changing validators’ PBC keys related to staked tokens at the predetermined intervals Stabilize ValueShuffle facilitating in the event of epoch change, ValueShuffle, fine-tuning of the Facilitator code Change PBC keys: network, Network, support for changing node’s pbc (validator) keys on the go Check for stale connections, Network, check if some neighbor connections are stale and re-connect Stress Testing: Deploy TxGenerator, Testing, transaction generator deployment support for devnets Use AONT (All or Nothing) for all serialized representation of secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets Implement WAU (Wipe After Use) for all secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets  Plans for Sprint 17</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 6 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 6 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the sixth Testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 5:
 Added HashCash challenge to PubSub protocol to limit denial-of-service attacks Implemented simplified Re-Staking for tracking validators&amp;rsquo; online status Implemented wallet recovery using 24-word recovery phrase Implemented wallet password protection and encryption of keys stored on disk Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 microSTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report May, 20th - May, 31st</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-20th-may-31st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-20th-may-31st/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period May, 20th — May, 31st:
Done in Sprint 17  Speed-up node bootstrap and re-synchronization, Node, fine-tuning bootstrap constants
 Service Awards, Core Blockchain, required to create an incentive for validators to be always online
 Compress Micro Blocks to Macro Blocks, Consensus, remove last epoch’s micro blocks by moving their data to a single macro block</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 22nd - May, 3rd </title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period April, 22nd — May, 3rd:
Done
 Finalize HashCash integration, Network, required to prevent DoS-attacks Stress Testing: Transactional Load Generator, Testing, the part of test harness Determine major blockchain constants: Maximum UTXOs per Block, Epoch Length &amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, those are important parameters of the consensus protocol Wallet Recovery, Wallet, required to recover wallet keys using 24-word recovery phrase Key Encryption on the Disk, Wallet, implement safe storage of keys on disk Proof of UTXO Construction, Wallet, a feature allowing to prove that a particular transaction has taken place in the past  In progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 8th - Apr, 19th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April,8th — April, 19th:
Done
 Kademlia DHT-based routing, Network, base networking functionality for unicast messages Research xPIR, Experimental, research the possibility of using private information retrieval protocols to secure light nodes Websocket Wallet API Enhancements Fork Resolution, Consensus, this is an essential part of the consensus protocol Rollback of Payment Transactions in Wallet, Wallet, this mechanism is needed due to fork resolution Limit the Number of Outputs in a Block, Core Blockchain, required to prevent traffic jams in the network Stabilize Network, Network, testing and bug fixing Stabilize Consensus, Consensus, testing and bug fixing Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 Units (microSTG), Core Blockchain, required to have fractional STG units  Plans for Sprint 15</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 5 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 5 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the fifth testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 4:
 Added a fork resolution mechanism to consensus and improved handling of network partitions. Implemented basic cheating detection of malicious validators in consensus (without punishment for now). Significantly reduced the time of full sync with the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Tech Report Mar, 25th - Apr, 5th”</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April, 2nd — April, 15th:
 Investigate packet loss in libp2p, Network, fixing a bug with lost packets related to the usage of Cuckoo-filters View Changes for Micro Blocks, Consensus, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol View Changes for Key Blocks, Consensus`, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol Determine Epoch Length &amp;amp;&amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, epoch length and block time are important parameters of the consensus protocol HashCash Algorithm, Network, nodes have to solve HashCash puzzles in order to join the network to prevent Sybil attacks Unicast Messages Encryption, Network, unicast messages traveling over Kademlia DHT network have to be encrypted Test cases for block validation, Core Blockchain, part of the functional testing harness RaptorQ Encoder/Decoder, Network, required to create optimized protocol for transmission of blocks/other large messages  In-progress:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech report Jan, 29th - Feb, 8th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period January, 29th — February, 8th:
 Core: Blockchain persistency. Blocks are stored on disk now but no transaction pruning is applied. Core: Node bootstrap. A new node can connect to any Stegos nodes to download the blockchain. Core: The special Data UTXO type has been removed and data functionality has been rolled into the payment UTXO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech report Dec,31st - Jan, 27th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</guid>
      <description>Dec,31st - Jan,13th, the Stegos development team has released the blockchain prototype (MVP). The MVP release containts the following base features:
 Nodes can select a group of validators among them Nodes can elect a leader of the consensus Nodes can verify incoming transactions The leader of consensus can create and propose blocks Validators can verify proposed blocks and co-sign them with their BLS signature The leader can form the final BLS multi-signature and broadcast sealed block to the network Nodes can verify and process incoming sealed blocks by pruning spent UTXOs out of the UTXO set  There is no disk persistance in the MVP release, as well as new nodes cannot connect and bootstrap from the living nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>