<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DEVELOPMENT on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DEVELOPMENT on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Security: Best Practices</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/practices/</guid>
      <description>Privacy and security go hand-and-hand, and the Stegos team is dedicated to ensuring the security of your Stegos nodes and funds, particularly when it comes to exchanges. But as with all crypto, ultimate responsibility lies with the user. Read on for some simple tips to help protect yourself against hackers and nefarious actors!
Our CEO Joel recently commented on the official Stegos Telegram channel about security measures, exchanges and how that translates to executive decisions by Stegos team, along with some strategies users can employ to protect their STG holdings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it Works: Gamified Proof-of-Stake (gPoS)!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/gpos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/gpos/</guid>
      <description>Cryptocurrency design is often focused on security, scalability and decentralization, and rightly so. But that’s not enough to build large networks which can last for the long haul. At Stegos, we know that a cryptocurrency network also needs to be fun, engaging, surprising, and rewarding. Our gamified Proof-of-Stake (gPoS) system is built with exactly these qualities in mind. Read on to learn more about what gPoS is, how it works, why a balance of risk and reward helps promote engagement and decentralization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Staking Pools FAQ</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq/</guid>
      <description>This week marked the launch of the Stegos staking pools. You can find the launch announcement here, along with all the details about our first pool, The Vault, and the huge bonuses it brings!
This announcement generated a lot of excitement in the community, but also a lot of requests for more details. Here are the answers to some of the most common questions. If you still want to know more, contact one of the admins on our Telegram group, or head to the forums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos验证池常见问题</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq_zn/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools_faq_zn/</guid>
      <description>本周标志着Stegos验证池的启动。您可以在此处找到启动公告，以及有关我们的第一个验证池 - 金库 的所有详细信息以及它能带来的丰厚奖励！
这个公告在社区中引起了很多热议，但也有许多要求提供更多详细信息的请求。以下是一些最常见问题的答案。如果您仍然想了解更多信息，请联系我们Telegram群中的管理员，或前往论坛。
如果您想参与，则需要在此处填写KYC表单，然后，您会收到官方验证池的申请表，这两个表单将引导您完成所有需要做的事情，您的STG会立即开始产生收益！
什么是Stegos验证池？ Stegos验证池是一个安全存储STG并获得奖励的地方，而无需您自己运行Stegos节点，我们将运行这些节点，您将获得奖励！
为什么要委托STG到stegos官方验证池？ 理由有很多！也许您不知道如何运行节点，不能从您所在的国家安全或轻松地运行节点，或者没有足够稳定的设备来获得验证者服务奖，也许运行节点的成本太高，或者您根本不想运行节点！
不管是什么原因，如果您持有STG却无法自己进行质押，那么将STG委托给Stegos官方的验证矿池是获得奖励的最好方法。Stegos链为节点们提供了巨大的激励机制，因此，如果您不将自己的STG进行质押挖矿，同时也不委托我们的矿池进行挖矿，您将失去很多机会。
委托到验证池有什么收益？ 绝对有！除了避免运行自己的节点的成本和困难之外，Stegos的每个验证池都有自己的基本收益和特殊奖励。我们的第一个验证池 - 金库，具有不同级别的委托奖励金，具体取决于您所选择的锁定代币的时间。
 1 个月锁仓期 - 0 手续费, 额外10%奖励 3 个月锁仓期 - 0 手续费, 额外50%奖励 6 个月锁仓期 - 0 手续费, 额外100%奖励  请务必注意，这些是基于您的验证奖励的额外奖励，而不是基于您本金的奖励。因此，如果您委托100万STG并通过6个月的锁定获得了250,000 STG的奖励，则提款的最终余额将为1,500,000 STG。
我需要完成KYC才能使用Stegos验证池吗？ 是的，使用验证池的每个人都需要完成KYC，可以在此处找到KYC申请表，完成填表操作后，我们将向您发送验证池申请表。
为什么需要完成KYC？Stegos不是隐私币吗？ 因为验证池是由Stegos提供的第一方保管服务，我们必须遵守欧洲的法规，我们正在紧急寻找一个解决方案，但不希望它推迟我们的验证池的启动。
请放心，这不会影响其余部分Stegos区块链的安全状态：Stegos上的交易和消息都是完全隐私的，在自己的节点上进行验证不需要KYC（永远不会）。
验证池的预期收益怎么计算？ Stegos是一个复杂的通证经济系统，有许多因素在共同起作用，这些因素包括VSA（这是一项高差异性奖项）和全球stake池的相对规模。因此，不可能给出一个准确的数字，我们也不能做出任何保证。但是，由于一致的区块时间为8秒，而每个区块的STG奖励为24 STG，因此最为保守的STG的年度回报率为10％。这是一个相对保守的估计，即假设全部流通量都在进行质押验证，并且一年下来你都没有赢得VSA（每个块12 STG），这两者都不太可能，所以几乎可以肯定真实收益率会比10%更高。
如果我使用验证池进行质押挖矿，我是否还能赢得验证者服务奖（VSA）？ 每种验证池将是一个节点，因此每个VSA周期都有一次机会来赢得验证者服务奖（VSA）。当一个验证池节点赢得VSA时，奖金将按比例分给奖池中的所有用户。
如果高概率赢得VSA的机会对您很重要，我们建议您运行自己的节点。我们将发布有关质押验证和VSA背后策略的常规技巧和建议，但是每个人都必须根据自身的情况来做决定，例如运行节点成本、可用stake数量和提供一个或多个稳定节点的能力（请记住，只有那些已经自上次VSA颁奖以来，在100％的区块中进行有效验证，才可以具备获得VSA的资格）。
我可以委托到多个验证池吗？ 不能。用户必须选择一个池来提交其STG，尽管用户可以将其委托代币从一个池移至另一个池，但前提是这不会破坏约定的锁定期。（用户可以移至锁定期较长的池，但不能移入较短的池。）
会有各种验证池吗？ 是的，我们计划推出各种各样的验证池，以便为不同层次、持有意愿、风险承受能力的参与者提供多样化的服务！ 第一个可用的池是金库（The Vault），这是一个相对简单的 - 但非常有好处的验证池，即在一个池中，您可以将令牌锁定1、3或6个月，以换取基于您的验证奖励的额外奖励。
我委托验证池后还可以自己运行节点进行验证吗？ 能。用户可以自由验证，也可以使用验证池。实际上，我们鼓励用户运行尽可能多的节点！
委托何时生效，委托后多久开始获得收益？ 委托实时生效，委托生效后立刻开始获得委托收益。
我的收益如何查看，收益是否可以随时赎回 一开始，需要Stegos团队的成员手动对余额进行检查。不久之后您将可以通过我们的Telegram机器人检查您的收入。
首先，目前只会提供三种验证池，分别要求在委托时选择锁定期为1个月，3个月或6个月。锁定期结束后，用户每天可以请求提款一次，本金和收益将在下一个工作日发送到您的帐户。
其他种类的池将很快启动，它们具有不同的规则，而且一开始就具备每日提币的能力。
委托后是否可以随时更换验证池？ 不能。一旦验证池实现完全自动化，我们可能会在以后推出此选项，但是即使那样，也只能更改为具有相同或更长锁定期的池。
收多少费用？ 目前stegos官方验证池完全免费。限时限额，先到先得！</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ready, Set, Stake!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/pools/</guid>
      <description>Don’t want to run a node? Don’t know how? Maybe you’re a little short on STG, or don’t have the resources or availability to run a reliable node of your own? Maybe you’ve got the opposite problem, and have some STG to spare? Don’t worry, we’ve got everyone covered. Stegos staking pools are here. While community infrastructure builds up in and around the Stegos network, we’re taking the initiative to put together a number of public staking pools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Discourse Forums Launch Announcement</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/discours-forums/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/discours-forums/</guid>
      <description>The Stegos Discourse Forums Have Arrived!
Stegos is a unique privacy network with many advanced and unusual features. This places Stegos a cut above the rest of the crypto pack, but it can also make it tricky for newcomers to just jump in. And for those who already know their way around our blockchain, it can be hard to find a place to discuss advanced topics or find the answers to tricky questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Holidays from Stegos</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/12/happy-holidays-from-stegos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/12/happy-holidays-from-stegos/</guid>
      <description>Dear community, From our Stegos family to yours, we wish you happiness and peace this holiday season!
Regardless of what you celebrate, we hope you get some private time to relax and spend time with friends and family as the year comes to an end.
News Rundown The end of the year has been extremely busy at Stegos HQ. Here’s some of the things you might have missed:
Mainnet Launch The Stegos mainnet launched in November, and everything went very smoothly, thanks to all the bug testing and feedback from the community during the hackathon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Release Notes</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-release-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-release-notes/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce the release of the Stegos mainnet.
Please download v1.0 of the Stegos desktop app by selecting the file from the Assets menu at the bottom of the page which matches your operating system.
New Users If this is your first time using the Stegos app, you don&amp;rsquo;t need to do anything else. Just download and install the app and you&amp;rsquo;re ready to go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Launched!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launched-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launched-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce the successful launch of the Stegos mainnet!
Head here to download v1.0 of the Stegos destkop app and get started. Existing users should delete their testnet chain data and restart their app: it will update automatically.
What Next? This week we&amp;rsquo;re concentrating on sending everyone their STG coins. If we need any information from you, the team will be in touch directly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Launch Announcement</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-launch/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, After thousands of hours of development work, months of testing and six weeks of intense feedback and updates courtesy of our wonderful Stegos community and the bounty and hackathon, we&amp;rsquo;re delighted to announce that the Stegos Mainnet will be launching on Wednesday 20th November!
STG Unlock Schedule We&amp;rsquo;re committed to a rapid unlock schedule to give everyone access to the STG they&amp;rsquo;ve bought and earned as soon as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 5 Launched!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-beta-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/mainnet-beta-5/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, This is the fifth beta release of the upcoming Stegos mainnet. Beta 5 is primarily a stabilization release, which fixes a major bug and brings many speed improvements. This release is fully compatible with Beta 4 Stegos blockchain and no other actions besides updating Stegos software is required from users.
Upgrading to Beta 5 is highly recommended, especially for participants of the bounty program.
Changes since Mainnet Beta 4:  Finally fixed DNS resolver on Windows Fixed multiple corner cases in consensus Fixed &amp;ldquo;entered unreachable code&amp;rdquo; bug Enabled log rotation for stegosd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Bounty and Hackathon Extended!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Dear Community, We hope you&amp;rsquo;ve been enjoying the bounty and hackathon so far. Thank you for all your excellent content submissions and signal boosting of our own content.
Our community and network have both grown enormously, and we&amp;rsquo;ve been able to make huge efficiency improvements to our app and chain based on your feedback and bug reports.
We&amp;rsquo;ve recently translated the bounty into Chinese to reach our community. Participation has been through the roof, with a consistent flow of new members signing up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 4 released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-4/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community! We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to announce the fourth beta release of the upcoming Stegos mainnet, which fixes a major bug and brings many speed improvements.
VERY IMPORTANT!!!: This release involves a complete restart of the chain, SO PLEASE READ THE NEXT SECTION EXTREMELY CAREFULLY OR YOU MAY LOSE YOUR TOKENS AND HACKATHON PROGRESS.
Steps to install the new release If you are already participating in the bounty If you are an existing participant of the bounty program and have already received bounty tokens to your Stegos wallet, you MUST BACK UP YOUR ACCOUNT, otherwise all of your bounty tokens will be permanently lost!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos $150k Bounty and Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/hackathon-bounty/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the Stegos $150,000 Bounty and Hackathon To celebrate our final testnet release before the upcoming Stegos IEO and mainnet release, we&amp;rsquo;re offering a $150,000 bounty program to help spread the word about Stegos and collect feedback on our app and blockchain.
The bounty program will run in two parts, each with a prize pool of $75,000 in STG coins. The two halves of the bounty program will run simultaneously, and you can take part in both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos News: $150k bounty and more!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3-and-150k-bounty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3-and-150k-bounty/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, Big news this week. The devs have released the next beta version of mainnet: Mainnet Beta 3. This will be the final test version of mainnet before our release. You can read the full release notes here.
This week also marks the launch of our bounty and hackathon, where you can complete tasks to earn a share of $150,000 of STG. The bounty will have two halves: a social media contest running on our website and powered by the Vyper competition platform, and a hackathon hosted on our very own mainnet beta chain and supported by a Telegram bounty bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 3 and App v0.14.0 Released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/10/mainnet-beta-3/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We&amp;rsquo;re please to announce our final beta release for the upcoming Stegos mainnet, as well as the next version of our desktop app (v0.14.0). The label &amp;ldquo;beta&amp;rdquo; means that we have no known critical issues and showstoppers. This is a complete restart of the chain, so all balances will be wiped. Users will have to delete their old chain data before restarting the app. The contents of the following directories must be deleted fully:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta 2 Released!</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/mainnet-beta-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/mainnet-beta-2/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, Thank you for all your testing feedback. We’re pleased to announce the release of Mainnet Beta 2. In addition to lots of improvements and UI tweaks, the most exciting feature of Mainnet Beta 2 is Windows support. So you can now use the app on Mac, Linux or Windows.
Please visit releases to download the app.
As always, please send comments, bug reports and any other feedback to support@stegos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Beta and Desktop App Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/first-desktop-app-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/first-desktop-app-beta/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, We’re excited to present the first version of the Stegos desktop app. Our development team have poured their hearts into making this, and now we’d love for you to help us test it. Please download the app and use the test STG faucet to get some test STG to put it through its paces! ​ This is the very first public version of the app, so it’s still a work in progress.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Progress Report July, 16th - August, 5th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/tech-report-july-16th-august-5th/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/tech-report-july-16th-august-5th/</guid>
      <description>Development Report July 16th – August 5th Hello, and welcome to the Stegos Development report for our 21st Sprint, covering the period from July 16th through August 5th.
We’ve mostly been concentrating on the Stegos GUI wallet. The Linux and iOS versions of the wallet are finished and being tested internally. Public testing will be announced shortly.
 Snowball improvements  We’ve been working to improve Stegos’ state-of-the-art mixing protocol, known as Snowball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stealth Mode Deactivated</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/88-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/88-news/</guid>
      <description>Dear Community, First of all, I&amp;rsquo;d like to apologize for the lack of updates: when you&amp;rsquo;re as serious about privacy as we are at Stegos, it can be hard to strike the right balance between secrecy and sharing! Rest assured, the whole team has been working hard behind the scenes on the Stegos chain, app, and a LOT of new marketing content, but I haven&amp;rsquo;t done a good enough job of keeping you, our loyal community, up to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 4</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/mainnet-4-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/mainnet-4-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a bug fix release, containing more than 100 fixes since Mainnet Preview 3.
Changes in Stegos v0.11:  Improved overall stability and performance of Snowball mixing protocol, now Snowball works reliably even on slow 3G/4G mobile data connections. Tuned core blockchain constants and limits to reach the inflation target, now a new block is produced every 6-8 seconds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Progress Report July, 1st - July, 15th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/tech-report-july-1st-july-15th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/07/tech-report-july-1st-july-15th/</guid>
      <description>Development Report July 1st – July 15th Hello, and welcome to the Stegos Development report for our 20th Sprint, covering the period from July 1st through July 15th.
The entire development team has been firing on all pistons in preparation for the launch of our mainnet. With the launch just a few weeks away, most of our hard work has been geared towards testing the blockchain and putting finishing touches to the Stegos app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 3</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-3-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-3-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a third Preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. In order to boost node synchronization and bootstrap performance we have switched to the new pairing curve, BLS12-381, reducing BLS signature verification by the factor of 40. Another major achievement was switching single curve crypto from Curve1174 to Curve25519 in order to increase Bulletproofs performance and provide a compatibility to iOS13 CryptoKit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report June, 17th - July, 1st</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-17th-july-1st/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-17th-july-1st/</guid>
      <description>Done in Sprint 19  Switched to new pairing-based crypto implementation based on BLS12-381 curve, [Crypto], 40x improvement in BLS signature verification time Switched to Dalek Curve25519 implementation for single curve crypto, [Crypto], 10x improvement in Bulletproof verification time, future compatibility with iOS CryptoKit Implemented of Payment Certificates in CLI Wallet, [Wallet], payment certificates are needed if you have to proof that you send a particular amount of tokens to somebody</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 2</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-2-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-2-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a second Preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. We declare the feature freeze with this release - no new features are planned until the upcoming mainnet release. Of course, some minor improvements and bug fixes will be made until the final mainnet release.
New in Stegos v0.9:  Node has been split into two binaries: a full node daemon (stegosd) and a command-line client (stegos).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report June, 3rd - June, 17th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-3rd-june-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/tech-report-june-3rd-june-17th/</guid>
      <description> Done in Sprint 18  Base functionality of GUI Wallet desktop application, Wallet, implementing bootstrapping visualisation, accounts and payments Persist Payment History and Payment Certificates in Wallet, Wallet, required to support showing the payment history in wallet Improve security of Docker image, Security, strengthen the security of the node&amp;rsquo;s docker image Introduce variable fees in transactions, Core Blockchain, Wallet, introduce the ability to set arbitrary fee amount for transaction in order to increase chances of transaction to be included in the nearest block Use Base58 for external representation of wallet public keys (addresses), Core Blockchain, provide more user-friendly encoding of addresses Implement WebSocket API Authorization, Security, introduce API tokens for authorizing WebSockets API usage, even on localhost Support changing the wallet password, Security, provide the ability for the user to change wallet password Stress Testing: Large Number of Nodes, Testing, part of test harness Split log output and CLI, Node CLI, separating CLI application from node binary Introduce variable fees in transactions, Core Blockchain, Wallet, introduce the ability to set arbitrary fee amount for transaction in order to increase chances of transaction to be included in the nearest block Speed up BLS signatures, Core Blockchain, BLS signature verification time has been improved from 200ms down to 5ms per signature  Plans for Sprint 19  Stress Testing: Packet Delay and Loss, Testing, part of test harness Stress Testing: Blockchain, Consensus, Service Awards, Slashing, ValueShuffle, Testing, stress testing the vital subsystems using transactional loads from transaction generator  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mainnet Preview 1</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-1-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/06/mainnet-1-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Mainnet Preview 1 Release Notes Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is a first preview release of upcoming Stegos mainnet. This preview version is considered mostly feature-complete. All core features have been implemented, yet some improvements and bug fixes need to be made for the final release.
New in Stegos v0.8:  Created an innovative blockchain compression technology to remove intermediate intra-epoch blocks after reaching the final pBFT consensus in validators group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 7 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-7-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-7-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the seventh testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 6:
 New StakeUTXO, Core Blockchain, StakeUTXOs with BLS signatures Public payment UTXO, Core Blockchain, UTXO with uncloaked recipient pubkey and amount Adding time locks to all UTXO types, Core Blockchain, allow UTXOs to be time-locked Introducing micro and macro blocks, Core Blockchain, adding more security to microblocks Slashing, Consensus, punishing the cheating slot owner for publishing two different blocks on the same height Re-Staking, Consensus, changing validators’ PBC keys related to staked tokens at the predetermined intervals Stabilize ValueShuffle facilitating in the event of epoch change, ValueShuffle, fine-tuning of the Facilitator code Change PBC keys: network, Network, support for changing node’s pbc (validator) keys on the go Check for stale connections, Network, check if some neighbor connections are stale and re-connect Stress Testing: Deploy TxGenerator, Testing, transaction generator deployment support for devnets Use AONT (All or Nothing) for all serialized representation of secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets Implement WAU (Wipe After Use) for all secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets  Breaking changes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report May, 6th - May, 17th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-6th-may-17th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period May, 6th — May, 17th:
Done in Sprint 16
 New StakeUTXO, Core Blockchain, StakeUTXOs with BLS signatures Public payment UTXO, Core Blockchain, UTXO with uncloaked recipient pubkey and amount Adding time locks to all UTXO types, Core Blockchain, allow UTXOs to be time-locked Introducing micro and macro blocks, Core Blockchain, adding more security to microblocks Slashing, Consensus, punishing the cheating slot owner for publishing two different blocks on the same height Re-Staking, Consensus, changing validators’ PBC keys related to staked tokens at the predetermined intervals Stabilize ValueShuffle facilitating in the event of epoch change, ValueShuffle, fine-tuning of the Facilitator code Change PBC keys: network, Network, support for changing node’s pbc (validator) keys on the go Check for stale connections, Network, check if some neighbor connections are stale and re-connect Stress Testing: Deploy TxGenerator, Testing, transaction generator deployment support for devnets Use AONT (All or Nothing) for all serialized representation of secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets Implement WAU (Wipe After Use) for all secrets, Security, additional security for in-memory representations of secrets  Plans for Sprint 17</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 6 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/testnet-6-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 6 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the sixth Testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 5:
 Added HashCash challenge to PubSub protocol to limit denial-of-service attacks Implemented simplified Re-Staking for tracking validators&amp;rsquo; online status Implemented wallet recovery using 24-word recovery phrase Implemented wallet password protection and encryption of keys stored on disk Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 microSTG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stegos Staking Pools Just Got MUCH Simpler</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/simpler-staking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2020/01/simpler-staking/</guid>
      <description>At Stegos, we are committed to making things intuitive and user friendly. Our staking pools were created to make staking as accessible as possible, but KYC requirements went against this. So we got rid of them. Aggressive pruning, network sharding, and fast data messaging all prepare the Stegos network for worldwide adoption. In order to see that level of activity, our ecosystem of software and applications must be as easy to use and accessible as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report May, 20th - May, 31st</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-20th-may-31st/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-may-20th-may-31st/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period May, 20th — May, 31st:
Done in Sprint 17  Speed-up node bootstrap and re-synchronization, Node, fine-tuning bootstrap constants
 Service Awards, Core Blockchain, required to create an incentive for validators to be always online
 Compress Micro Blocks to Macro Blocks, Consensus, remove last epoch’s micro blocks by moving their data to a single macro block</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 22nd - May, 3rd </title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/05/tech-report-apr-22nd-may-3rd/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
Here is what we accomplished in the period April, 22nd — May, 3rd:
Done
 Finalize HashCash integration, Network, required to prevent DoS-attacks Stress Testing: Transactional Load Generator, Testing, the part of test harness Determine major blockchain constants: Maximum UTXOs per Block, Epoch Length &amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, those are important parameters of the consensus protocol Wallet Recovery, Wallet, required to recover wallet keys using 24-word recovery phrase Key Encryption on the Disk, Wallet, implement safe storage of keys on disk Proof of UTXO Construction, Wallet, a feature allowing to prove that a particular transaction has taken place in the past  In progress</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech Report Apr, 8th - Apr, 19th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-apr-8th-apr-19th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April,8th — April, 19th:
Done
 Kademlia DHT-based routing, Network, base networking functionality for unicast messages Research xPIR, Experimental, research the possibility of using private information retrieval protocols to secure light nodes Websocket Wallet API Enhancements Fork Resolution, Consensus, this is an essential part of the consensus protocol Rollback of Payment Transactions in Wallet, Wallet, this mechanism is needed due to fork resolution Limit the Number of Outputs in a Block, Core Blockchain, required to prevent traffic jams in the network Stabilize Network, Network, testing and bug fixing Stabilize Consensus, Consensus, testing and bug fixing Split 1 STG to 1 000 000 Units (microSTG), Core Blockchain, required to have fractional STG units  Plans for Sprint 15</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testnet 5 Release</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/testnet-5-release/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Testnet 5 Release Notes
Stegos creates cutting-edge technology that keeps your secrets safe from prying eyes so you feel empowered and secure.
This is the fifth testnet release of the Stegos blockchain. Changes since Testnet 4:
 Added a fork resolution mechanism to consensus and improved handling of network partitions. Implemented basic cheating detection of malicious validators in consensus (without punishment for now). Significantly reduced the time of full sync with the network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Tech Report Mar, 25th - Apr, 5th”</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/04/tech-report-mar-25th-apr-5th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period April, 2nd — April, 15th:
 Investigate packet loss in libp2p, Network, fixing a bug with lost packets related to the usage of Cuckoo-filters View Changes for Micro Blocks, Consensus, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol View Changes for Key Blocks, Consensus`, view change is an essential part of the consensus protocol Determine Epoch Length &amp;amp;&amp;amp; Block Time, Consensus, epoch length and block time are important parameters of the consensus protocol HashCash Algorithm, Network, nodes have to solve HashCash puzzles in order to join the network to prevent Sybil attacks Unicast Messages Encryption, Network, unicast messages traveling over Kademlia DHT network have to be encrypted Test cases for block validation, Core Blockchain, part of the functional testing harness RaptorQ Encoder/Decoder, Network, required to create optimized protocol for transmission of blocks/other large messages  In-progress:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech report Jan, 29th - Feb, 8th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/02/tech-report-jan-29th-feb-8th/</guid>
      <description>During the last two weeks our development team has been working hard to finalize major features of the upcoming testnet release.
The following tasks were completed in the period January, 29th — February, 8th:
 Core: Blockchain persistency. Blocks are stored on disk now but no transaction pruning is applied. Core: Node bootstrap. A new node can connect to any Stegos nodes to download the blockchain. Core: The special Data UTXO type has been removed and data functionality has been rolled into the payment UTXO.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tech report Dec,31st - Jan, 27th</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/01/tech-report-dec31st-jan-27th/</guid>
      <description>Dec,31st - Jan,13th, the Stegos development team has released the blockchain prototype (MVP). The MVP release containts the following base features:
 Nodes can select a group of validators among them Nodes can elect a leader of the consensus Nodes can verify incoming transactions The leader of consensus can create and propose blocks Validators can verify proposed blocks and co-sign them with their BLS signature The leader can form the final BLS multi-signature and broadcast sealed block to the network Nodes can verify and process incoming sealed blocks by pruning spent UTXOs out of the UTXO set  There is no disk persistance in the MVP release, as well as new nodes cannot connect and bootstrap from the living nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>