<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>interview on </title>
    <link>https://stegos.com/tags/interview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in interview on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stegos.com/tags/interview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Differ AMA</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/ama-crypto-differ/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/ama-crypto-differ/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, Last week, our CEO Joel conducted a series of AMAs in various communities. Here&amp;rsquo;s the transcript of his AMA with Crypto Differ on Monday 18th November.
We start with three intro questions from our team, to present briefly Stegos to the CryptoDiffer community
Can you introduce yourself to the community? What is your background and how did you start Stegos ??
 Good morning! I’m the founder and CEO of Stegos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crypto Daku AMA</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/ama-daku/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/11/ama-daku/</guid>
      <description>Dear Stegos Community, On November 18th, our CEO Joel took part in a Telegram AMA for Crypto Daku. The transcript of that AMA is provided below:
Transcript AMA Crypto Daku - 18.11.2019
Which types of updates you&amp;rsquo;ve done in recently launched mainnet beta 5 as compared to previous beta versions?
 Good morning everyone! The event updates were very much focused on the stability of the mainnet and improvements to sync times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of AMA with BlockArk</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/ama-with-blockark/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/09/ama-with-blockark/</guid>
      <description>At 7pm on September 17th, Stegos founder Joel conducted a 100-minute AMA live broadcast to the community. It was broadcast simultaneously across 9 different communities, with a peak viewership of 4,500 people as Joel shared the twists and turns of creating Stegos. The technical details of Stegos and the live Q&amp;amp;A discussion format made for an exciting evening. Below you&amp;rsquo;ll find a transcript of last night&amp;rsquo;s AMA.
This guest for this time is Joel, who is the founder of Stegos, an experienced hacker and blockchain pioneer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMA session conducted over Telegram and Wechat, August 14, 2019</title>
      <link>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/ama/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stegos.com/news/2019/08/ama/</guid>
      <description>Host ： Hello, and welcome to this Stegos community AMA event. Our AMA is about to begin! Please don’t post messages during the AMA. We will begin by answering the questions we collected in advance, followed by a 15-minute quickfire question session to conclude the AMA.
Host ：Please welcome Stegos CEO Joel Reymont!
Host ：Hi Joel, welcome to the community and this AMA!
To start, Joel will outline Stegos&amp;rsquo; current status and future development vision, and share his experience of starting Stegos.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>